export const Question = [
  // 1
  {
    prompt: "In compiling a program, the first step that must be done is:",
    optionA: "Creating programs",
    optionB: "Creating Algorithms",
    optionC: "Buying a computer",
    optionD: "Process",
    answer: "B",
  },
  // 2
  {
    prompt: "A definite step-by-step procedure for solving a problem is called:",
    optionA: "Process",
    optionB: "Program",
    optionC: "Algorithm",
    optionD: "Diagram",
    answer: "C",
  },
  // 3
  {
    prompt: "The pseudocode used in writing the algorithm is:",
    optionA: "English",
    optionB: "Poetic Language",
    optionC: "Programming language",
    optionD: "Machine Language",
    answer: "C",
  },
  // 4
  {
    prompt: "In making computer programs, algorithms are made:",
    optionA: "Before programming",
    optionB: "When the program is created",
    optionC: "After programming",
    optionD: "When it's run",
    answer: "A",
  },
  // 5
  {
    prompt: "Instruksi P=Q akan mengakibatkan nilai P=nilaiQ,dan nilai Q menjadi :",
    optionA: "Be Any Value",
    optionB: "Become empty",
    optionC: "Fixed Q",
    optionD: "Fixed P",
    answer: "D",
  },
  // 6
  {
    prompt: "If a = 5, b = 10, then if given the instruction a = b; b=a will result in:",
    optionA: "a=0 , b=5",
    optionB: "a=10 , b=5",
    optionC: "a=10 , b=0",
    optionD: "a=10 , b=10",
    answer: "D",
  },
  // 7
  {
    prompt: "Given the algorithm P=10; P=P+5; Q=P. The P and Q values are respectively:",
    optionA: "15 and 0",
    optionB: "0 and 15",
    optionC: "15 and 15",
    optionD: "0 and 10",
    answer: "C",
  },
  // 8
  {
    prompt: "the first structure in pascal is ...",
    optionA: "Uses crt;",
    optionB: "String",
    optionC: "End.",
    optionD: "Char;",
    answer: "A",
  },
  // 9
  {
    prompt: "To see the results of the program you are working on, press the ...",
    optionA: "CRTL+F5",
    optionB: "CRTL+F9",
    optionC: "CRTL+F2",
    optionD: "CRTL+F12",
    answer: "B",
  },
  // 10
  {
    prompt: "How many codes are used to make the color text 'CYAN'...",
    optionA: "4",
    optionB: "128",
    optionC: "3",
    optionD: "7",
    answer: "C",
  },
  // 11
  {
    prompt: "A simple basic command in the passcal program is ...",
    optionA: "Readln",
    optionB: "End",
    optionC: "Write",
    optionD: "Writeln",
    answer: "C",
  },
  // 12
  {
    prompt: "The Pascal language data type for TRUE FALSE is ...",
    optionA: "String",
    optionB: "Boolean",
    optionC: "Char",
    optionD: "Byte",
    answer: "B",
  },
  // 13
  {
    prompt: "The structure of the very first Pascal programming language is ...",
    optionA: "Var;",
    optionB: "Writeln;",
    optionC: "End;",
    optionD: "Uses crt;",
    answer: "D",
  },
  // 14
  {
    prompt: "Pascal's data type for characters is ...",
    optionA: "Char",
    optionB: "Boolean",
    optionC: "Integer",
    optionD: "Byte",
    answer: "A",
  },
  // 15
  {
    prompt: "When was Pascal formed?",
    optionA: "1981",
    optionB: "1971",
    optionC: "1961",
    optionD: "1991",
    answer: "B",
  },
];
